

DANIEL NICOLAS DIAZ

DATA ANALYST JR.

L 319 447-7860



Manielnicolasmuner@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

I am a Jr. Data Analyst with Python. I have experience in data processing in the health sector with personal projects. I seek to apply my acquired knowledge in terms of data exploration, whether stored on servers or web traffic in real-time, as well as share my skills and creativity through collaborative work.

EXPERIENCE

PERSONALIZED DENTISTRY

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Partner

- Data reports regarding the health benefits information system in Colombia.
- Establish initiatives for the proper handling and storage of patient data.
- Sales reports using SQL queries in Google Sheets.

SITEL GROUP

Apr 2020 - Dec 2021

Customer Service Advisor Phone

- Provide solutions to customers in the different digital or printed subscriptions.
- Establish relationships with the client to improve their expectations with the brand.

GERDAU DIACO

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

Automation Intern in Steel Industry

- Industrial network connections for drive management through logic programmers and Siemens HMI interfaces.
- Management of schedules and budgets in automation projects in steel cooling systems.
- Strategic planning for opening an instrumentation laboratory specialized in industrial measurement sensors.

EDUCATION

DATA ANALYST - PLATZI

2021 - 2022

- Analyze structured data to identify patterns and trends.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN MECHATRONIC ENGINEERING - UNIAGRARIA

2013 - 2018

- Automation, robotics, IoT, embedded systems.

LINUX SERVER ADMINISTRATION - PLATZI

2022 - 2022

- Linux distributions most used in servers. Manage packages according to the distribution. Configure tools to monitor processes and services.

GOOGLE ANALYTICS - ANALYTICS ACADEMY

2022 - 2022

- Google Analytics Academy

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

LANGUAGES

Fluent English & Native Spanish

DATE OF BIRTH

March 14, 1995

MARITAL STATUS

Single

LEISURE TIME

No way to skip a good basketball game .

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/danielnicolasmunevar/

WED SIDE

kind-stone-04621511e.1.azurestaticapps.net/